<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>christophercampbell</title><link>https://cdcampbell.io/</link><description>Recent content on christophercampbell</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cdcampbell.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First post!</title><link>https://cdcampbell.io/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcampbell.io/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Hello! This is where I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting updates on what I like to call my &amp;lsquo;research loop&amp;rsquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be rotating between IoT hacking, bug bounties, and purposefully vulnerable machines (stuff like HackTheBox) to get my name out there for exploit authoring, blogs, and conference talks. More content soon!</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://cdcampbell.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcampbell.io/about/</guid><description>Details I like to go places I don&amp;rsquo;t belong, so I was a natural fit for hacking and infosec. I enjoy making apps behave in ways they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed as much as I enjoy providing readable, workable feeedback for clients in ways they can understand (something the USMC taught me).
I do application, network, and systems security assessments and engineering for Independent Security Evaluators, a security consultancy. As part of my work, I publish blog posts whenever I have interesting findings or useful advice to share.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cdcampbell.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcampbell.io/contact/</guid><description>Feel free to contact me with any questions about any of my projects.
I am not currently looking for a new job, but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind providing some independent counsel.
I can be emailed at ccampbell@cdcampbell.io, but I frequently check messages on the other listed platforms on my Home page.
My current local time is &amp;laquo;TO FILL IN&amp;raquo;.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://cdcampbell.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcampbell.io/projects/</guid><description>I will log the start dates of research projects and other educational milestones here. Use these to find relevant blogposts about how I began the project.
March 2020 Dating/Encounter Application Enumeration</description></item></channel></rss>